Sergio Nicolás Galindo Cante

Software Developer | Desarrollador Web

|Email |LinkedIn: NicolasGalindo.in |Tel:+57 312 5293348 |Page: /nicolas-galindo

Bogotá, Colombia

Durante mi trayectoria como desarrollador y creador digital, eh tenido la oportunidad de colaborar en proyectos con importantes empresas en Colombia como AXA Colpatria y suramericana.

En mi experiencia profesional, eh trabajado junto con los clientes siempre cumpliendo con las expectativas en el desarrollo de los proyectos. Con una trayectoria de 1 año y 8 meses en el ámbito de programación, llevo a cabo proyectos en Back-End y Front-End a nivel profesional. Con habilidades en entornos cooperativos con un excelente trabajo en equipo y una excelente comunicación asertiva. Aplico conocimientos en implementación de pruebas automatizadas y patrones de diseño (MVC). Utilizo tecnologías como: Java, Springboot, Python, Liferay, JavaScript, React, CSS, HTML, Bootstrap, Git, SQL, Adobe, Figma.

During my career as a developer and digital creator, I have had the opportunity to work on projects with major companies in Colombia such as AXA Colpatria and Suramericana.

In my professional experience, I have worked with clients who have always met their expectations in the development of projects. With a trajectory of 1 year and 8 months in the programming field, I carry out projects in back-end and front-end at a professional level. With skills in collaborative environments with excellent teamwork and assertive communication. I apply my knowledge of automated test implementation and design patterns (MVC). I use technologies such as: Java, Springboot, Python, Liferay, JavaScript, React, CSS, HTML, Bootstrap, Git, SQL, Adobe, Figma.

Professional Experience

VASS Company, Bogotá, Colombia

Liferay Developer / May 2023 - Oct 2023

- Collaborated in creating ADTs and Templates in **Liferay CMS 7.4** for **EPS SURA**. Contributed to user stories and project management.
- Developed widgets, fragments, and themes to optimize the portal interface and participated in the implementation of remote applications to expand system functionality.

AXA Colpatria, Bogotá, Colombia

Liferay Developer (Intern) / Oct 2022 - Mar 2023

- Assisted in building ADTS fragments and templates in CMS Liferay versions 7.2, 7.3.
- Created a basic MVC portlet widget for internal portals.

Education

Technologist in Software Development.

Servicio Nacional de Aprendizaje (SENA) 2023-03-15.

Programación con Python para el Análisis de Datos.

(Desafío Latam) 2024-05-14

Java web Service.

(LinkedIn) 2023-03-02

Languages

English: Intermediate (B1).

Core Skills

Java, Flutter, PHP, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, React, Springboot, Gradle, Git, MySQL, Adobe, Figma, Teamwork, Communication, Problem Solving